♪ ...don't know who she is ♪
♪ Or how she is ♪
♪ Or when, what, why she is ♪
♪ But as for where she is, she is where we will go ♪
♪ To Adelaide! ♪
♪ Come on and join the Adelaide parade♪
- No.
♪ Adelaide! ♪
♪ To Adelaide! ♪
♪ Let's go to Adelaide's house ♪
I need to fix that last part,
but that's the idea.
So, Beatrice, you sing you sing the high parts
Wirt, you sing the really high part.
What?
Oh.
- And...
- Nobody is singing anything anymore.
And, Wirt, keep moving.
But I-I have to...
...ugh.
Alright.
- But we have to do something fun.
- You know, we really don't.
We can just keep walking silently, you know?
And... ugh.
Wirt, let's go. Come on.
Sorry, sorry.
But shouldn't we...
Greg, don't you want to be more like your brother?
...just always doing what you're told.
Huh?
...just a pathetic pushover to make all his decisions.
Hey! What? I'm not a pushover.
Hold on, Wirt. Let me get to my point.
Ugh, fine.
See, Greg? No willpower whatsoever
Hrmph!
You need to be more like that.
But that doesn't really sound that fun.
The world is a miserable place, Greg.
Life isn't fun.
Then I'll do what I need to do, I guess.
Thank you.
We'll just focus on getting you guys to Adelaide's
so I can wash my hands of this whole affair.
And if you could pick up the pace a bit,
that'd be great, okay?
Okay?
Hey, where's Greg?
Oh. Uh, wondered off, I guess.
Cheese and crackers!
We need to do our part to make the world a better place!
Graawr
Ha ha, yeah.
Huh? Whoa!
School?!
Pssh! Not today.
Greg!
Greg! Greg?
Oh.
- Greg?
- Excuse me?
Please, take your seat, children.
You're late.
You know the rules...
"once the bell has rung, class has begun."
Oh, sorry, everybody. Sorry.
No, he doesn't have a brain. He can't learn anything.
Let's go, Wirt. Come on. Here, boy.
What? Did you say something?
I can't hear you because I'm too busy doing what I'm told.
What? What are you...
No, no. Let's go.
Oh, no. See, I'm a pushover, remember?
I have to do what she tells me to do.
ugh...
Wirt, your brother could be in trouble somewhere.
tap, tap, tap, tap
Mnh-mnh-mnh, mnh-mnh.
Ha ha! Yeah!
Bluebird's have a short life span.
You two are literally killing me
every moment I'm forced to spend with you.
Oh.
Young man, I will not stand for such nonsense in my classroom.
I've got enough nonsense from that
no good, two-timing, low-down, handsome man of mine.
Oh, Jimmy Brown, why did you have to leave me so?
And now, with my father threatening to close the school
and that wild gorilla on the loose,
why, Jimmy, I just have one thing to say...
♪ "A" is for the apple that he gave to me ♪
♪ but I found a worm inside ♪
♪ "B" is for beloved that♪
♪ I called to him before... ♪
Ouf. That lady's got some baggage.
What's that?
Young man, go to the dunce box.
Oh. Sure!
- Okay! sure.
- No, no. No, no, no.
[ Wirt Humming ]
Aw.
Now, where were we?
Oh, yes.
♪ "G" is for the gentleman I thought he was ♪
♪ when he first said hi... ♪
So, my theory is
hot dogs are not actually dogs,
regardless of what they teach you in school.
But you guys don't go to school, huh?
I'm gonna stick with you guys.
Ha ha!
Hey, I got an idea.
Let's play two old cat.
Do you guys know how to play two old cat?
It's fun. I'll show you.
Here we go.
Here's one old cat.
Meowr
Mrowr
You found another one!
Wait. No.
I think that cat is too old.
Mrrrowwr
Sorry, kitty. We'll have to find another old cat.
Hey, Jeffrey, I think there's one behind you!
RaaAAAGH
Gorilla!
Run!
♪ ...and "Y", yes "why"♪
♪ is the question that's on my mind ♪
♪ Oh why... ♪
Hey, dunce! This is dreadful!
Good, I'm glad you feel that way.
Hmph
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding
♪ ...I remember life with y- ♪
Ahpf!
Huh! Gorilla!
Raaaaagh
Mealtime already?
Well, come along children.
Ow!
We don't want to be late for mealtime.
My father will be visiting today,
and we'll need to be on our best behavior.
Quick! In here!
Oh, boy! Mealtime!
This is way better than being chased by a gorilla.
Aw, what's the matter?
Mm. Kind of bland.
Hey, nobody ordered you to eat yet.
Yeah, but...
Ohh.
Hey! I know what to do!
Here Ms. Langtree, Play something like this.
Oh, like this?
Mm... good enough.
♪ oh, potatoes and molasses ♪
♪ if you want some, oh, just ask us ♪
♪ they're warm and soft like puppies and socks ♪
♪ filled with cream and candy rocks ♪
♪ oh, potatoes and molasses ♪
♪ they're so much sweeter than algebra class ♪
♪ if your stomach is grumblin' ♪
♪ and your mouth starts mumblin' ♪
♪ there's only one thing ♪
♪  to keep your brain from crumblin' ♪
♪ oh, potatoes and molasses ♪
♪ if you can't see 'em put on your glasses ♪
♪ they're shiny and large like a fisherman's barge ♪
♪ you know you eat enough when you start seeing stars ♪
♪ oh, potatoes and molasses ♪
♪ it's the only thing left on your task list ♪
♪ they're short and stout, ♪
♪ They'll make everyone shout! ♪
♪ for potatoes ♪
♪ and molasses ♪
♪ for potatoes and... ♪
-That's enough!
- Father!
Is this what I've been paying for?!
Hey! We just wanted to have a little fun.
I didn't invest in this school for "fun".
I thought we were trying to do important work here
teaching animals to count and spell.
We are! Oh, please, father, don't close the school.
It won't happen again.
I should say it won't.
- This...
- Pbht!
...this...
- Meow!
...and this are all coming with me.
Now send them to bed!
You heard father. Off to bed with you.
I just wanted to have fun,
change the world, and make it a better place.
But I just made everything worse.
Ruh Raow
Okay, Wirt, I'll admit it ...
you seem like a pushover,
- but you're not.
- Oh?
Deep down in your heart,
you're a stubborn jerk!
When are going to give this up?!
Maybe never. Maybe I'll never give this up.
Hmm...
Yeah!
Wirt's right! Never give up!
Come on, Wirt.
Let's go save the day.
Okay, if you say so!
pfft
Come on.
So, what's the plan, Greg?
Plan?
- Ohh. I don't know.
-Oooooww
Who would've thought making a
primer school for animals was a bad idea?
My life savings, my home...
everything I had went into that dear, dear school.
And now I'm forced to sell these instruments just to keep it open.
All the while that loathsome Jimmy Brown
is off gallivanting who knows where!
Not to mention that wild gorilla on the loose.
If only something would go right for a change.
Zzzzzz
Okay, I think he's asleep.
Let's go steal his stuff.
- What?
The instruments!
They've been stolen!
Who would do such a thing?!
Huh?
- Here you go.
- Oh, here you go, sonny.
What is this?
It's a benefit concert for the school.
Haah, isn't it grand.
All these fine people giving out of the goodness of their hearts?
Not like my Jimmy Brown.
Oh, here we go.
All he ever did was steal my heart away.
Gorilla!
Young man, do something!
Uh...
Whoa!
- Huh!
Ugh... finally!
Jimmy?
That's right, darlin'.
I was the gorilla.
But why did you do it?
Got a job in the circus so's I could finally buy ya that wedding ring.
But when I got stuck in the dang suit,
everybody was too doggone scared to help me out.
Oh, Jimmy.
- Oh!
- Darlin'.
Yeah!
I guess the world really is as sweet
as potatoes and molasses.
♪ Oh, potatoes and molasses ♪
♪ if you want some... ♪
So, want me to tell Greg it's time to get going?
Nah, let him have his fun.
♪ ...filled with cream and candy and rocks ♪
- Hey, Wirt.
- Yeah?
- Tie your shoe.
- Hmm? Oh. Mm. Okay.
♪ ...algebra class ♪
♪ if your stomach is grumblin' and your mouth... ♪